<resources>
    // App name
    <string name="app_name">Software Engineering Quiz</string>

    // Title
    <string name="title">How likely you are to enjoy work as a software developer</string>

    // Quiz Objective
    <string name="objectiveSubTitle">Quiz Objective</string>
    <string name="objective">This is a personality quiz to know if coding could be right for you;
        here are 10 signs that aren\'t always accounted for in academic tests. Be honest answering it,
        you would be only lying to you\'re self if not.</string>

    // EditText View
    // User Name
    <string name="editNameText">Name</string>

    // Question 1
    <string name="question1">Are you a problem-solving person?</string>
    <string name="answer1">Lots of people will simply tolerate problems without
        looking for a proactive way to solve them, particularly if tolerating
        the problem is easier. If you don\'t take this approach, but actually
        enjoy the challenge of solving problems of all kinds, then that\'s a great
        sign that you could be suited to software development. If, in your desire
        to solve problems, you also take into account realistic constraints, such
        as timeframes and budgets, then this could be a real asset in your search
        for a career.</string>

    // Question 2
    <string name="question2">Do you have a passion for strategy games?</string>
    <string name="answer2">Yes, it can be true that gaming is good for you,
        particularly where strategy games are concerned. These help hone your
        ability to make decisions based on a number of relevant factors, taking
        into account both short and long-term consequences. As well as computer
        games, those who enjoy offline games like chess, bridge or risk, could
        also have an underlying aptitude for programming. At Net-a-porter, for
        example, we even have a weekly games club.</string>

    // Question 3
    <string name="question3">Do you have a musical mind?</string>
    <string name="answer3">While the evidence for the correlation between music
        and maths is still in debate, it seems commonplace for those with musical
        talent to have mathematical abilities too. In our team, there are numerous
        coders who either compose music, sing, or play an instrument.</string>

    // Question 4
    <string name="question4">Do You have a talent for winning arguments?</string>
    <string name="answer4">If have a logical approach to arguing your points in a
        structured way means that you frequently win over your opponents, this could
        be a sign that you have the systematic thinking needed for software
        development.</string>

    // Question 5
    <string name="question5">Do you love making things?</string>
    <string name="answer5">You can get the same sense of satisfaction from making
        something in the virtual world as you can in the physical world. Indeed,
        in the digital world, you aren\'t constrained by practicalities like materials
        and space, so imagination is your only limit. Having a natural curiosity for
        how things work, and how to make them work better, is a good indication of a
        nascent software developer.</string>

    // Question 6
    <string name="question6">Are you a people person?</string>
    <string name="answer6">Contrary to the stereotype of the IT team hidden away from
        the rest of the company, working as a developer can actually involve a great
        deal of interaction with others across the business. This means that an enjoyment
        of communicating and an ability to explain things in a way that is easily
        understood by others, are both really important.</string>

    // Question 7
    <string name="question7">Would you like to know more about the theory of computer science?</string>
    <string name="answer7">While you may not have digested the full history of computer science,
        an interest in the theory behind software engineering is an important aspect of a coder\'s
        skillset. You don\'t want to spend your time re-inventing the wheel, so being interested
        in what others have discovered, and being prepared to build on those foundations, will fast-track
        your potential achievements.</string>

    // Question 8
    <string name="question8">Are you a team player?</string>
    <string name="answer8">Coding itself is a very collaborative process; continuously reviewing
        and redefining code with others helps you to shake out bugs, makes your work more likely
        to meet users\'s needs and is one of the best ways to learn. Developers therefore need to
        enjoy working together and should be prepared to study, critique and improve one another's work.</string>

    // Question 9
    <string name="question9">Are you intrinsically motivated?</string>
    <string name="answer9">Putting some amateur psychology to use, it seems to be true that the
        best developers are intrinsically motivated. This means they take their reward and
        motivation from the process of finding a solution to a problem, or creating something
        innovative in itself. In other words, developers often do what they do for the love of
        doing it, rather than just being paid to do it.</string>

    // Question 10
    <string name="question10">Do you love technology?</string>
    <string name="answer10">This is fairly obvious, but it is worth re-iterating that if you want
        to work in software engineering, you need to have an appreciation for the amazing
        possibilities that technology brings to the world. Being interested in how you can harness
        the potential of technology, for whichever company you want to work in, will definitely
        stand you in good stead, and is a sure sign you are on the right career track for success
        in coding.</string>

    // Likert Scale
    // RadioButton Group
    <string name="likert1">Almost Never True</string>
    <string name="likert2">Usually Not True</string>
    <string name="likert3">Occasionally True</string>
    <string name="likert4">Usually True</string>
    <string name="likert5">Almost Always True</string>

    // SwitchView
    <string name="showExplanation">Show Explanation</string>

    // ButtonView Text
    <string name="button">Analyze</string>

    /Message constructor
    <string name="messageIntro">Thank you for being honest</string>
    <string name="messageLikert1">, your answers indicate that you will strongly dislike a career in software engineering</string>
    <string name="messageLikert2">, your answers indicate that you will moderately dislike a career in software engineering</string>
    <string name="messageLikert3">, your answers indicate that you will may enjoy a career in software engineering</string>
    <string name="messageLikert4">, your answers indicate that you will moderately enjoy a career in software engineering</string>
    <string name="messageLikert5">, your answers indicate that you will strongly enjoy a career in software engineering</string>




</resources>
